<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Virtual Tour of UQ</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_ar_fragment">TODO replace with AR camera for barcode scanning</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gmaps">Map</string>

    <string name="location_prompt">Choose a location</string>
    <string-array name="location_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>13</item>
        <item>14</item>
        <item>15</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Information Strings-->
    <string name="great_court">
    The construction of the Great Court complex was a statement by the Queensland Government and the university that Queensland intended to take tertiary education seriously and that Queensland was an equal of other Australian states.
        The Great Court is a unique space of historical and cultural importance which has now influenced generations of students and staff through its powerful gravitas and iconic power.
    </string>

    <!--Information Strings-->
    <string name="forgan_smith">
    Construction of the Forgan Smith building on the St. Lucia campus of The University of Queensland began in 1937.
        It remains the main building on the campus and when it was first built was one of the most impressive in any Australian university.
        During its century of existence, the university has produced many histories. The largest was produced in its seventy-fifth year, authored by Malcolm Thomis.
        For its hundredth year, The University of Queensland produced a short, largely pictorial, study by Ben Robertson.
    </string>

    <string name="gp_south_rover_room">
        Room where most ITEE students come to work on their assignments.
        Tutors are here available for help for most programming courses.
        This room is best known for the 3010 - Rover inident on 2016.
    </string>

    <string name = "gp_south_building">
    Built to house primarily Engineering and Information Technology Faculties the building is extensively serviced with over 140 kilometres of data cabling.  Electrical reticulation was carefully designed to minimise electromagnetic interference to data and personnel.

    The building houses the basis of a centralized Chilled Water Precinct to serve this region of the campus, with space and infrastructure to support expanded capacity in the future.
    An innovative control system feature allows reduction in air conditioning loads and costs where spaces are not constantly occupied.
    </string>
    <string name="museum">
        Originally known as the Darnell Collection, The University of Queensland Art Collection began in the 1940s as the result of a generous financial bequest by John Darnell.
        While funds were originally applied to endow a special library collection, the University redirected the remainder of these funds towards establishing a Fine Art Library.
        Dr JV Duhig, Professor RP Cummings and Professor HC Richards, assisted by a group of artists and advisors, within a few years assembled a collection of some 400 works.
        At the time, The University of Queensland did not have an art museum, and the collection was hung in the main geology lab at the University\'s original home in George Street.
    </string>

    <string name="lakes">
        The Freshwater Lake is one of the iconic features of the St Lucia campus.
        You may have seen it countless times before but take a moment to learn the lessons it can teach us.
        There is much history from the species that were native to the area, some of which remain and there are new species which originate from beyond Australian shores.
        The St Lucia lakes are an example of an aquatic ecosystem in action.
        Modified with the intention of managing stormwater runoff and to provide aesthetic amenity, the lakes are now home to a number of aquatic animals.

    </string>



    <!--Vuforia stuff-->
    <string name="button_start">Start</string>
    <string name="activities_list_title_string">Vuforia Samples</string>
    <string name="activities_list_empty">No activities</string>

    <string name="button_OK">OK</string>

    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_AUTHORIZATION_FAILED_TITLE">Authorization Error</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_PROJECT_SUSPENDED_TITLE">Authorization Error</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_NO_NETWORK_CONNECTION_TITLE">Network Unavailable</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_SERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE_TITLE">Service Unavailable</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_UPDATE_SDK_TITLE">Unsupported Version</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_TIMESTAMP_OUT_OF_RANGE_TITLE">Clock Sync Error</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_REQUEST_TIMEOUT_TITLE">Request Timeout</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_BAD_FRAME_QUALITY_TITLE">Poor Camera Image</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_UNKNOWN_TITLE">Service Unavailable</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_AUTHORIZATION_FAILED_DESC">The cloud recognition service access keys are incorrect or have expired.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_PROJECT_SUSPENDED_DESC">The cloud recognition service has been suspended.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_NO_NETWORK_CONNECTION_DESC">Please check your internet connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_SERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE_DESC">The service is unavailable, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_UPDATE_SDK_DESC">The application is using an unsupported version of Vuforia.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_TIMESTAMP_OUT_OF_RANGE_DESC">Please update the date and time and try again.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_REQUEST_TIMEOUT_DESC">The network request has timed out, please check your internet connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_BAD_FRAME_QUALITY_DESC">The camera does not have enough detail, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_UNKNOWN_DESC">The service is unavaiable, please try again later.</string>

    <string name="INIT_ERROR">Error</string>
    <string name="INIT_ERROR_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED">Failed to initialize Vuforia. This device is not supported.</string>
    <string name="INIT_ERROR_NO_CAMERA_ACCESS">Failed to initialize Vuforia. Camera not accessible</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_MISMATCH_KEY">Vuforia App key is not valid for this product. Please get a valid key, by logging into your account at developer.vuforia.com and choosing the right product type during project creation.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_MISSING_KEY">Vuforia App key is missing. Please get a valid key, by logging into your account at developer.vuforia.com and creating a new project.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_INVALID_KEY">Invalid Key used. Please make sure you are using a valid Vuforia App Key.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_NO_NETWORK_TRANSIENT">Unable to contact server. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_NO_NETWORK_PERMANENT">No network available. Please make sure you are connected to the Internet.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_CANCELED_KEY">This app license key has been canceled and may no longer be used. Please get a new license key.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_PRODUCT_TYPE_MISMATCH">Vuforia App key is not valid for this product. Please get a valid key, by logging into your account at developer.vuforia.com and choosing the right product type during project creation.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_UNKNOWN_ERROR">Failed to initialize Vuforia.</string>
    <string name="INIT_OBJECT_DATASET_NOT_FOUND_TITLE">Database not found</string>
    <string name="INIT_OBJECT_DATASET_NOT_FOUND">Please scan an object and load a database</string>

    <string name="content_desc_camera_button">Camera Button</string>
    <string name="overlay_build_target_help">Hold the device parallel to the target</string>
    <string name="target_quality_error_title">Low Quality Image</string>
    <string name="target_quality_error_desc">The image has very little detail, please try another.</string>

    <string name="menu_back">Vuforia Samples</string>
    <string name="menu_extended_tracking">Extended Tracking</string>
    <string name="menu_character_mode">Character Mode</string>
    <string name="menu_flash">Flash</string>
    <string name="menu_flash_error_on">Unable to turn on flash</string>
    <string name="menu_flash_error_off">Unable to turn off flash</string>
    <string name="menu_contAutofocus">Autofocus</string>
    <string name="menu_contAutofocus_error_on">Unable to activate Continuous Auto-Focus</string>
    <string name="menu_contAutofocus_error_off">Unable to deactivate Continuous Auto-Focus</string>
    <string name="menu_datasets">DATASETS</string>
    <string name="menu_camera">CAMERA</string>
    <string name="menu_camera_front">Front</string>
    <string name="menu_camera_back">Rear</string>
    <string name="menu_button_red">Red</string>
    <string name="menu_button_blue">Blue</string>
    <string name="menu_button_yellow">Yellow</string>
    <string name="menu_button_green">Green</string>

    <string name="splash_screen_description">Vuforia Splash</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
</resources>
